Lilly Library collection of press kits and other film media releases, 1975-1995 PN1997 .A1
Lilly Library
- Press kits and other film media releases, 1975-1995
  - The Russia House (Box 15)
  - Russkies, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Ruthless People, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Rustlers Rhapsody, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - The Sandlot (Box 15)
  - Santa Claus: The Movie, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - The Santa Clause, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Sarafina! (Box 15)
  - Satisfaction (Box 15)
  - Say Anything (Box 15)
  - Say Yes, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Scenes from a Mall, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Scent of a Woman, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Schindler's List, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - School Daze (Box 15)
  - School Ties (Box 15)
  - The Scout (Box 15)
  - Sea of Love, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Secret Admirer, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - The Secret Garden (Box 15)
  - See No Evil, Hear No Evil, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - The Serpent and the Rainbow, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - The Seventh Sign, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - The Shadow, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Shakedown, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Shattered (Box 15)
  - She-Devil, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Sheena (Box 15)
  - She's Out of Control, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Shining Through (Box 15)
  - Shipwrecked, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Shocker, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Shoot to Kill, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Short Circuit, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Short Circuit 2, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Shout, Includes photographs or glossy prints (photographs damaged) (Box 15)
  - Sibling Rivalry, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - The Sicilian (Box 15)
  - Sign O' the Times, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - The Silence of the Lambs, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Silver Bullet, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Silverado, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - A Simple Twist of Fate, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Sing, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Single White Female (Box 15)
  - Sioux City, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Sister Act, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Sister Act 2: Back in the Habit, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Sister Sister, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Six Degrees of Separation, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Sixteen Days of Glory (Box 15)
  - Sixty-Eight, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Ski Patrol, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Skin Deep (Box 15)
  - Sleeping Beauty ( Re-Release), 1986; Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Sleeping with the Enemy (Box 15)
  - Sleepless in Seattle (Box 15)
  - Sleepwalkers (Box 15)
  - Slugger's Wife, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Smokey and the Bandit Part III, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Sniper (Box 16)
  - Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs ( Theatrical Re-Release), 1987; Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 16)
  - So I Married an Axe Murderer (Box 16)
  - Soapdish, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Solarbabies (Box 16)
  - A Soldier's Story, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Someone to Watch Over Me, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Something Wild (Box 16)
  - Son-in-Law, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Son of the Pink Panther (Box 16)
  - Song of the South ( Theatrical Re-Release), 1986; Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Sophie's Choice, (original folder damaged/torn) (Box 16)
  - Soul Man, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Space Camp, Includes slides (Box 16)
  - Spaceballs (Box 16)
  - Spaced Invaders, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Species (Box 16)
  - Speechless (Box 16)
  - Speed (Box 16)
  - Speed Zone, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Spies Like Us, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Splash, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Split Second (Box 16)
  - Splitting Heirs, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Squanto: A Warrior's Tale, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - The Squeeze, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - St. Elmo's Fire (Box 16)
  - Stakeout (Box 16)
  - Stand by Me, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Star Trek V: The Final Frontier (Box 16)
  - Star Trek VI: The Undiscovered Country, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Star Trek Generations (Box 16)
  - Starman (Box 16)
  - State of Grace (Box 16)
  - Staying Together (Box 16)
  - Stealing Home, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Steel Magnolias, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Stella (Box 16)
  - Stick (Box 16)
  - Stone Cold, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Stop! Or My Mom Will Shoot, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Straight Talk, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Stranded, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - A Stranger Among Us (Box 16)
  - Street Fighter, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - A Streetcar Named Desire - Director's Cut, (1993); Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Streets of Gold, Includes slides (Box 16)
  - Strike It Rich, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 16)
  - Striking Distance (Box 16)
  - Stronghold, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - The Stunt Man, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Suburban Commando (Box 16)
  - Sugar Hill (Box 16)
  - Summer Rental, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Summer School, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Sunset, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - The Super (Box 16)
  - Super Mario Bros., Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Supergirl (Box 16)
  - Superman (Box 16)
  - The Sure Thing, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Surrender (Box 16)
  - Suspect, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 16)
  - Sweet Dreams, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Sweet Hearts Dance, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Sweet Liberty (Box 17)
  - Swing Kids, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Switching Channels, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Sylvester, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Tai-Pan, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Taking Care of Business, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - The Taking of Beverly Hills, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Tales from the Darkside: The Movie, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Tales from the Hood, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Tall Tale: The Unbelievable Adventures of Pecos Bill, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Tank Girl, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Tap, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Target, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Teachers (Box 17)
  - Teen Wolf Too, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - The Temp, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Terminal Velocity, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - The Terminator, (original folder torn/damaged) (Box 17)
  - Terminator 2: Judgment Day, Includes photographs or glossy prints (materials damaged) (Box 17)
  - Terror in the Aisles, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - That Was Then - This Is Now, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - That's Dancing! (Box 17)
  - Blake Edwards's That's Life!, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Thelma & Louise (Box 17)
  - They Live, (materials damaged) (Box 17)
  - Thief of Hearts, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - The Thin Blue Line (Box 17)
  - The Thing Called Love, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - This Is My Life (Box 17)
  - Three Amigos, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Three Fugitives, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Three Men and a Baby, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Three Men and a Little Lady, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - The Three Musketeers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Three Ninjas (Box 17)
  - Three Ninjas Kick Back (Box 17)
  - Three O'clock High, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Throw Momma from the Train, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Thunder Run, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Thunderheart (Box 17)
  - Tie Me Up! Tie Me Down! (Box 17)
  - A Tiger's Tale, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Tightrope (Box 17)
  - Timecop, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Tin Men, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - To Live and Die in L.A. (Box 17)
  - Tom and Jerry - The Movie (Box 17)
  - Tombstone, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Tommy Boy (Box 17)
  - Top Dog (Box 17)
  - Top Gun, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Torch Song Trilogy, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Total Recall, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Tough Guys (Box 17)
  - Tough Guys Don't Dance, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Toy Soldiers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Toys (Box 17)
  - Trail Mix-Up (Box 17)
  - Trapped In Paradise (Box 17)
  - Trespass (Box 17)
  - Trick or Treat, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - Troop Beverly Hills, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - True Believer, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 17)
  - True Identity (Box 17)
  - True Lies (Box 17)
  - Truth or Dare (Box 17)
  - Tucker: The Man and His Dream, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Tuff Turf (Box 18)
  - Turk 182!, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Turner & Hooch, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Twins, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - The Two Jakes, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Two Thousand Ten (Box 18)
  - UHF, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - The Unbearable Lightness of Being, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Uncle Buck, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Under Cover, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Under the Cherry Moon, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Undercover Blues (Box 18)
  - The Unholy (Box 18)
  - Universal Soldier (Box 18)
  - Unlawful Entry (Box 18)
  - Untamed Heart (Box 18)
  - The Untouchables, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Used People (Box 18)
  - V.I. Warshawaski, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Valmont, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - The Vanishing (Box 18)
  - Vibes, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Vice Versa (Box 18)
  - A View to a Kill (Box 18)
  - Village of the Damned (Box 18)
  - Violets are Blue, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Vision Quest (Box 18)
  - Volunteers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (original folder water damaged) (Box 18)
  - Waiting for the Light (Box 18)
  - Wall Street (Box 18)
  - Wanted: Dead or Alive, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - The War of the Roses, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - WarGames (Box 18)
  - Warm Nights on a Slow Moving Train, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Wayne's World (Box 18)
  - Wayne's World 2 (Box 18)
  - Weekend at Bernie's (Box 18)
  - Weekend at Bernie's II (Box 18)
  - Welcome Home Roxy Carmichael, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - We're No Angels, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - What About Bob?, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - What's Eating Gilbert Grape (Box 18)
  - What's Love Got to Do With It, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - When a Man Loves a Woman, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - When Harry Met Sally..., Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - While You Were Sleeping, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Whispers in the Dark (Box 18)
  - White Fang (Box 18)
  - White Fang 2: Myth of the White Wolf, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - White Men Can't Jump (Box 18)
  - White Mischief, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - White Nights, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - White Palace, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Who Framed Roger Rabbit?, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Who's Harry Crumb?, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Who's That Girl? (Box 18)
  - Why Me?, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - The Wicked (Box 18)
  - Wild Hearts Can't Be Broken, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - The Wild Life (Box 18)
  - Wildcats (Box 18)
  - Willow (Box 18)
  - Winter People, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Wired (Box 18)
  - Wisdom, Includes slides (Box 18)
  - Wise Guys (Box 18)
  - Without a Clue, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Witness, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - The Wizard (Box 18)
  - Wolf (Box 18)
  - Working Girl (Box 18)
  - The Wrong Guys, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 18)
  - Year of the Dragon (Box 18)
  - Young Guns (Box 18)
  - Young Guns II (Box 18)
  - Young Sherlock Holmes (Box 18)
  - Youngblood (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous press kits, studio tour information, general materials relating to film; some items include photographs and slides. (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous press kits, studio tour information, general materials relating to film; some items include photographs and slides. (Box 20)
  - Arachnophobia (Box 21)
  - Article 99 (Box 21)
  - Avalon (Box 21)
  - Awakenings (Box 21)
  - Baby (Box 21)
  - Backdraft (Box 21)
  - Barton Fink (Box 21)
  - The Bear (Box 21)
  - Best Seller (Box 21)
  - Blind Date (Box 21)
  - Breakin' 2 (Box 21)
  - Born on the Fourth of July (Box 21)
  - Cabin Boy (Box 21)
  - Camp Nowhere (Box 21)
  - The Cemetery Club (Box 21)
  - Chaplin (Box 21)
  - The Commitments (Box 21)
  - Cool Runnings (Box 21)
  - Country, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 21)
  - Crimes and Misdemeanors (Box 21)
  - D2: The Mighty Ducks (Box 21)
  - Dead Poets Society (Box 21)
  - Deceived (Box 21)
  - Die Hard 2: Die Harder (Box 21)
  - Do the Right Thing (Box 21)
  - Enemies, A Love Story (Box 21)
  - Extremities (Box 21)
  - Fantasia: The 50th Anniversary (Box 21)
  - The Fabulous Baker Boys (Box 21)
  - Father of the Bride (Box 21)
  - Fire Birds (Box 21)
  - The Fisher King (Box 21)
  - Flatliners (Box 21)
  - For the Boys (Box 21)
  - F/X, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 21)
  - FX2: The Deadly Art of Illusion (Box 21)
  - Glory (Box 21)
  - Green Card (Box 21)
  - The Grifters (Box 21)
  - Hannah and Her Sisters (Box 21)
  - Happily Ever After (Box 21)
  - HAVANA (Box 21)
  - Hellraiser (Box 21)
  - Hiding Out (Box 21)
  - Home Alone (Box 21)
  - House II: The Second Story (Box 21)
  - Houseguest (Box 21)
  - The Jerky Boys: The Movie (Box 21)
  - King Ralph (Box 21)
  - Legend of Billie Jean, Original folder damaged/torn (Box 21)
  - Light of Day (Box 21)
  - The Longshot (Box 21)
  - Maxie (Box 21)
  - Mermaids (Box 21)
  - The Midnight Run for Charity (Box 21)
  - Miller's Crossing (Box 21)
  - Mischief (Box 21)
  - Mo' Better Blues (Box 21)
  - Mr. Destiny (Box 21)
  - The Muppet Christmas Carol (Box 21)
  - Murphy's Law (Box 21)
  - Music Box (Box 21)
  - My Left Foot (Box 21)
  - My Girl (Box 21)
  - No Man's Land (Box 21)
  - Parenthood (Box 21)
  - Porky's Revenge (Box 21)
  - Postcards From the Edge (Box 21)
  - Pretty Woman (Box 21)
  - The Prince and the Pauper (Box 21)
  - The Prince of Tides, 2 copies (Box 21)
  - Quiz Show (Box 21)
  - Rain Man (Box 21)
  - Real Genius (Box 21)
  - Red Heat (Box 21)
  - Renaissance Man (Box 21)
  - The Rescuers Down Under (Box 21)
  - The Silence of the Lambs, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 21)
  - Spacecamp (Box 21)
  - Steel Magnolias (Box 21)
  - Stone Cold (Box 21)
  - Super Mario Bros. (Box 21)
  - Sweet Dreams, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Original folder damaged (Box 21)
  - Taking Care of Business (Box 21)
  - Terminator 2: Judgment Day (Box 21)
  - Total Recall (Box 21)
  - Turk 182 (Box 21)
  - V.I. Warshawski (Box 21)
  - The War of the Roses (Box 21)
  - When a Man Loves a Woman (Box 21)
  - Young Guns (Box 21)